const e="crk",a=200,i=24,o=[{id:24,question:"He shall save his people from their sins. Who is being referred to here? ",option:{a:"John the Baptist ",b:"Elijah ",c:"Elisha ",d:"Jesus                              "},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:25,question:"The person who the Bible calls the son of consolation is ",option:{a:"Barsabas ",b:"Barabbas ",c:"Barnabas ",d:"Bathsheba"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:26,question:"Who do people say the son of man is? Jesus asks this question to know people’s ",option:{a:"desires ",b:"demand  ",c:"mind ",d:"opinion"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:27,question:"In Peter’s teaching,” God…………..the proud and gives grace to the humble",option:{a:"receives ",b:"relegates ",c:"resists ",d:"restores."},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:28,question:"The lesson which Jesus teaches in the parable of the Good Samaritan is that your neighbor is",option:{a:"only your friend  ",b:"your next of kin  ",c:"a distant friend ",d:"anyone who needs your  help"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:29,question:"Amram and Jochebad gave birth to : ",option:{a:"Mirian ",b:"Jedida ",c:"Jethro ",d:"Hur"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:30,question:"The two Hebrew midwives instructed by pharaoh to kill the Hebrew male babies at birth were:",option:{a:"Zipporah and Pauh ",b:"Pauh and Miriam ",c:"Shiphrah and Zipporah ",d:"Shiprah and Puah"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:31,question:"Israel went into Assyrain captivity in ",option:{a:"71AD ",b:"720BC ",c:"722BC ",d:"68AD"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:32,question:"Daniel was delivered from the den of lions for all the following reason except ",option:{a:"his holiness and faith ",b:"his kindness ",c:"God’s love for him ",d:"God’s mighty power"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:33,question:"Which of the following carried Judah into captivity ",option:{a:"Pharaoh Neco of Egypt ",b:"Goliath of Philistia ",c:"Assyrian ",d:"Nebuchadnezzar of Babylon"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:34,question:"The last things which Zedekiah saw before his eyes were removed was the ",option:{a:"Egyptian army ",b:"slaughter of all his sons ",c:"city of Jerusalem ",d:"feasting of the children of Israel "},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:35,question:"The prophet who was with the exiles of 597 BC in Babylon was ",option:{a:"Moses ",b:"Hosea ",c:"Micah ",d:"Ezekiel."},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:36,question:"The king of Persia who made it possible for the return of the exiles from Babylon was ",option:{a:"Dairus ",b:"Cyrus ",c:"Zechariah ",d:"Zerubabel"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:37,question:"The meaning of Emmanuel is ",option:{a:"laughter ",b:"“for I draw him from water ",c:"God with us ",d:"the fear of God"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:38,question:"“Bring your necks under the yoke of the king of Babylon and serve him and his people and live” who gave this advice? ",option:{a:"Jeremiah ",b:"Isaiah ",c:"Ezekiel ",d:"Amos"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:39,question:"One of the following said: “the lion has roared who will not fear? The Lord has spoken, who can  but prophesy?” ",option:{a:"Nathan ",b:"Jeremiah ",c:"Amos ",d:"Hosea"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:40,question:"Where did Paul cure a slave girl who had a spirit of divination ",option:{a:"Philippi ",b:"Ephesus ",c:"Athens ",d:"Antioch"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:41,question:"Joshua’s first victory was over the people of ",option:{a:"Ai ",b:"Gibeon ",c:"Gilgal ",d:"Jericho"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:42,question:"Josiah’s reign was popular because of his ",option:{a:"allies ",b:"victory ",c:"violence ",d:"reforms"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:43,question:"The meaning of Ephphatha is ",option:{a:"be opened ",b:"be still ",c:"be silent ",d:"little girl, arise"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:44,question:"Who baptized the Ethiopian Eunuch? ",option:{a:"Paul ",b:"peter ",c:"Philip ",d:"Rufus"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:45,question:"Moses fled from pharaoh at the age of ",option:{a:"45",b:"40",c:"85",d:"120"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:46,question:"Which of the following prophets was described as weeping prophet? ",option:{a:"Amos ",b:"Ezekiel ",c:"Jeremiah ",d:"Zephaniah."},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"},{id:47,question:"Who was the priest that confronted Uzziah in the temple ",option:{a:"Zadokaul ",b:"Phineas ",c:"Azariah ",d:"Aaron"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme",examyear:"2007"}],t={subject:e,status:200,total:24,data:o};export{o as data,t as default,a as status,e as subject,i as total};
